# Vitor Fernando da Silva

Brazil



vitor fernando@outlook.com.br



linkedin.com/in/vitor-fernando-da-silva

# **Summary**

I've been in contact with programming since 2015 and since 2019 I've been working with it.

I have experience in small and big software, object-oriented programming, creating and consuming REST APIs, high-performance applications and multi-threaded systems.

- Solid knowledge in React.js, Node.js and PostgreSQL;
- Work experience in backend development (PHP, Laravel, Python, Delphi);
- Work experience in frontend development (Javascript, AngularJS);
- Work experience in relational databases (MySQL, Oracle);
- Work experience in git (GitHub, GitLab);
- Work experience in agile methodologies (Scrum, Kanban);

# **Experience**



# **Software Developer**

# Nelogica

Jun 2021 - Jun 2023 (2 years 1 month)

Nelogica is a company that delivers software for high performance electronic trading. Here I worked in two different teams, "Homebroker" and "Project", maintaining and improving our microservices.

- In the homebroker team I created specific solutions for brokers, requiring constant alignment with our customers. I also did refactorings in order to optimize and standardize the brokers code.
- In the project team I developed solutions that improved the product as a whole, for that I worked with developers from other areas such as database and front end.

# is Design

### **Full Stack Developer**

### isDesign Softwares

Jan 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 5 months)

IsDesign Softwares is a company that works with the development and maintenance of e-commerce, personalized websites with CMS, personalized systems, native mobile applications.

- I worked on the systems of most of our customers, from the smallest to the largest, mainly developing new features and fixing bugs.
- I taught Git and Github to my co-workers to start using them in our projects.

# Full Stack Developer

Webermag

Feb 2019 - Dec 2019 (11 months)

At Webermaq, I worked on an application called Heimber, which is a store integrator that simplifies the process of advertising a product in large e-commerces.

• Worked on the development of essential functionalities such as order and product management and integration with the e-commerces and post office systems.

# **Education**



# IFRS

Technologist, Software Analysis and Development 2019 - 2022



# JStack

2023 - 2023

Full-Stack Development focused in React and Node

### **Licenses & Certifications**

The Complete Web Developer in 2022: Zero to Mastery - Udemy

UC-e592c6fd-9edb-4c1c-862f-71d17f54d0d3

# **Skills**

Full-Stack Development • Backend Development • React.js • Node.js • PHP • JavaScript • Git • Delphi • REST APIs • MySQL